abyssinica.com 2017-07-08

# Kekros Systems Privacy Policy

Kekros Systems, LLC (“Kekros”) operates the “Service,” which consists of cloud services, IT services, including web, mobile Apps, websites, software, database, as well as research, development, consulting and analytical capabilities that are utilized in conjunction with the above. Your privacy is important to us and it is our policy to respect the privacy of our users. By using Kekros, you consent to the practices described in this statement. Our Privacy Policy is designed around these principals: 

  * We collect personal identification only if and when it is required to register a product or meant to be used as data in the creation of an agreed-upon development or marketing solution; 
  * We don’t share, sell, rent or lease your personal information except if necessary to comply with the law, or to protect our rights;
  * We don’t market to our customers.

**Gathering of Non-Personally Identifying Information**  
Kekros collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available (“Analytics”), such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Kekros's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our websites. Kekros also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses; however, this information is not used to personally identify or market to our visitors. Rather, it is used to protect us against spam and to help us to better understand our audience geographically. 

**Protection of Certain Personally Identifying Information**  
Kekros takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of personally identifying information. Kekros will not rent, lease or sell potentially personally-identifying and/ or personally-identifying information to anyone. Kekros discloses personally identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on Kekros’s behalf. By using Kekros, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Kekros discloses personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Kekros believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Kekros.

**Ads**  
We do not provide any personally identifying Customer or User information to advertisers or to third-party websites. Ads appearing on Kekros may be delivered by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Kekros, and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Security of Your Personal Information**  
Kekros secures the personally identifying information you provide in a controlled environment, which is protected from unauthorized use or disclosure. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Kekros encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Service and/or continued provision of personally identifying information to us will be subject to the Terms of Use and the-current Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
